Thank you for watching.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen, the morning time has rung, and it's us.
We are the masses.
Before we begin, I'd like to announce today's mc of the day.
Yes, one and two. Vote for your favorite.
Here's one and two.
We'll keep them hidden.
That's right, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up
Sorry, sorry, sorry
We're allowed to watch.
We can look?
We can look.
Is that what this is about?
Don't let them see.
I'm not supposed to say anything.
You're not supposed to know what you're looking at.
Oh, really? - Yes.
Yes, it's been a while, hasn't it?
It's been a year and a half. I've never been in a con system before.
Oh, yeah, it says “Invisible.
Hey, from an amateur.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm sorry. I've just come back from a series of conventions, and they've finally changed the program system.
Sorry.
I'm not nervous.
I'm sorry to introduce you to the system.
This one and two we can see now.
We can see you.
Yes, we can see you.
Vote for your favorite.
Please.
Whoever has the number tag with that number on it...
Is today's MC.
Let the voting begin!
Let's start!
It's been a little too long, I haven't been here that long. Since last June?
Yes, that's right. Since last June is fine.
So, you know, I honestly think everyone should vote for 2. Honestly, everyone should vote for 2.
Wait a minute.
Everyone should vote for 2.
Huh?
Honestly, hey. Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes. All right, then. Five, four, three, two, one.
Okay. Okay, everybody, the results of the voting. Huh? Huh? Huh?
I kind of saw it already. 1?
I'm 1 in the voting results. That's right,
I'll be the MC today.
I'll be your MC today.
It's been a year and a half since I've been on the show, so I'm almost like a regular or a guest,
I think of myself as a regular or a guest on the show.
Is that possible?
So, please take it easy on me.
I'm sure there are a lot of things I don't know.
So I'm going to do mc again until the last time...
ah ah ah ah, and yes, I'm Shizuki number 15, in Kazami.
Let's get started!
Let's start with the showroom of a delightful married couple in the middle of a shrimp.
Thank you very much for visiting the 75th Ebichu's Delightful and Married Couple Showroom today.
This is our sister show, the showroom of our sister show, Ukka's Showroom.
Yes, sir.
Okay, so let's spread the word here.
In order to get as many people as possible to watch this show, we're going to make an announcement on the official Ebichu website now, so please spread the word.
Please spread the word!
I'd like to take a picture of you, but I'm not sure how to pose.
Pose?
Okay.
It's been a year and a half.
I'll decide.
Thank you very much. Now, if you guys could spread the word...
If you spread the word, you'll get an X on your Twitter account.
They don't have them at all. They don't have them anymore.
Really? I've been in a different country?
Have you been anywhere? Thank you for spreading the word.
He's left me behind. I miss it.
Urashima Taro Kamita.
Thank you for the 2,896 people, nearly 3,000, who've already watched today.
What are people even looking at anymore?
What?
Three thousand.
Oh, no, you're not? What are these stars?
The excitement quotient.
Rise Index?
Wait, I didn't know that.
What is this thing that we're looking at right now?
It's a red star with a number written on it, and it's the index of excitement.
I wonder what's at the top. Thank you.
Thank you.
It's not the number of people.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure the reason why so many people are watching today is because we're going to open our late-night show to the public.
We'll be showing it later in the show, around the time of the ending, so please don't miss it.
So please don't miss it until the end.
Now, let's get to the project.
Let's have a fun and funny survey talk!
Before the talk, we'll take a survey to decide what we'll talk about.
That's what “Survey Talk” is.
Okay, here's today's questionnaire.
Here's today's questionnaire. It looks like this.
Today, the second half is all handwritten by us.
I'm a little concerned about bad dreams.
Let's vote on what we'd like to hear.
Let's see...
Well, the top one is the live shows. We had three shows in November. That's a lot.
There's a lot we haven't really talked about, so I'm sure there's something you'd like to hear.
I'm curious... What do you want to hear?
I'm curious... what you want to tell Rika, or what you think Rika has in common with you... and many of you have guessed me, because it's been a while.
So let's vote.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Ta-da!
Let's see...
Yes, ma'am.
Did you get it?
Uh, number two?
Number 9?
Rika, it's been a year. What's going on?
This?
Your first move?
It's been a year and a half.
I want to tell you something.
A lot has happened in the past year, hasn't it?
December is almost here.
So...
Well...
Something that has been on my mind for a long, long time
I've been wondering...
What is it?
TP's Go for it Radio
TP's Go-Go Radio
It's been a hit with me and my manager.
It was a hit.
TP is a writer...
TP is a writer who's offline right now.
I was hoping that TP would say “Go for it!
I was hoping that the president would tell him to do his best, but it's been a year, and I was wondering when we should talk about this.
When are we going to talk about this?
Yes, TP is working hard with Mr. Sakurai.
I don't know if he's in the showroom right now...
We had a lot of meetings afterwards to reflect on what we'd done.
We received many kind words of appreciation.
I thought that I had never been told to do my best.
I would really like to get a live “ganbatte” from you.
This is the most important thing I wanted to tell you during the year and a half I was away from the showroom.
Yeah, the most.
So, I'm sorry. May I have it?
Ebichu, go for it!
Thank you!
You have the biggest smile of the day, right here.
Thank you! I'm so happy!
Yay!
Please listen to Bastand FM everyone!
TP's go-getter radio.
It's close.
I'm a fan too.
When... for the past year and a half...
I'm wondering when I'll be able to get on the air.
I can't wait to tell everyone how much I love this radio show.
Tell me about it.
I've been thinking...
That's so sweet.
TP, I'm trying my best.
Please let me be a guest sometime.
Seriously?
Please do!
So let's continue.
I'm happy now.
I could change it anytime today.
I'm so satisfied.
But by the way, you can choose again
You can choose again.
You can, right?
Oh, really?
Yes, you can.
You can do it one more time.
A little bit.
I don't have anything else.
Okay, let's start voting.
How many days?
Yes, please.
What do you think?
Okay.
For all the people who told me not to go home yet...
What do you have?
I'm curious.
Monta's fan level just went up to 10.
Congratulations. That's the 10th time in 9 months.
You don't seem like much of a reader.
I'm not supposed to read this.
I really shouldn't.
I'm too much of a liar.
Okay, that's the deadline... three more to go... 21.
You don't have to read this.
I'll do my best!
I'm going to read this... about the Akita Bunko Final!
I've got proper live feedback, right?
Well, you know. Akita Bunko, which we have been a part of for a long time, has finally reached its finals.
Yes, it was.
It was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
It was a lot of fun.
I don't know, this time we had a lot of collaborations like before,
It was a lot of fun to be able to talk with everyone in our free time and to collaborate even just a little bit.
It was fun. I knew it, Miyuki.
Yes.
From our Akita Bunko's point of view, she is a big star.
That's right.
I had collaborated with Miyuki Fujiwara many times on various songs, and this time, at the end, we were able to collaborate again on Deka Donden,
I think that was the most memorable moment for me.
She always wears a beautiful kimono, and this time she wore that kimono, so Miyuki was on stage at the beginning of the show,
So, Miyuki was on stage at the first opening, and she changed her kimono again for the collaboration with Ebichu. Yes, it was supposed to be a lot of work.
Yes, it was supposed to be a lot of work. She was wearing a completely beautiful different kimono.
I was thinking how cute and beautiful she looked wearing it, and Miyuki's singing voice was amazing.
No, really? The volume of her voice.
She really flies. It's great, isn't it? When Miyuki was about to say “Dawn”, she asked Miyuki to sing alone, and we were sent flying, and it was amazing.
Of course it was amazing, but the actual performance was several times, dozens of times more amazing. But the actual performance was several times, dozens of times, more than that. The power in his voice was incredible.
The “high energy” in his voice was so strong that it was like a burst of high energy.
But what was really great about Akita Bunko was the hospitality of the performers, which is something I usually reflect on when I think about the opposite,
The people of Akita are so kind and they welcome us like we are their family.
Every time we go there, they send us gifts and souvenirs.
And this year, Miyuki always sends us in Iburi school.
This year, she brought rice balls with salt and daikon pickles.
Yes!
It was too delicious, wasn't it?
I wonder if it was very well-pickled!
That's right.
We have a lot of people in the shrimp club.
They packed a lot of food in Ziplocs.
As you can imagine, we couldn't eat that many pickles in one day.
I said, “I'll take some home on your behalf.
I took some home with me.
That day, I went back to my parents' house.
So...
I had my family pick me up.
I opened the car, and when I got in...
I thought...
It smells like my grandma's, right?
Oh, pickles.
I didn't even notice it.
It was my own fault for managing the pickles, but I should have put them in several layers, but instead I just put them in a Ziploc bag and a plastic bag, and then put them in a paper bag.
So the whole time, the bullet train smelled like pickles.
All over the train.
That kind of thing.
Grandma's scent all the time.
A gentle scent.
Warm.
Really.
But you know, the pickles are really good.
So the next day, too.
I eat breakfast and dinner with my family.
But I told them that it was delicious with pickles.
But I also use the rice-ball salt that I got from the rice-ball salt
Just the other day, I wanted to make onigiri with freshly cooked rice, so I took it to my lesson.
It was so delicious!
It was delicious!
It had a little bit of sweetness to it, didn't it?
I'll try my best to have a live concert in Akita, even if it's not in the form of Akita Bunko.
I'm going to paint it, and I even got a sticker from Mr. Cabibula and Mr. Go!
So much love!
Thank you very much!
We'll do our best to come back.
We'll do our best.
Well, can I go ahead and do one more of these?
Yes, we'll set up a survey. Okay, let's go one more.
One more.
There was like a few millimeters difference, right?
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's start.
Please. I didn't get the keypicker sticker.
I want one.
I want this one.
I want it.
What do you think?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, you want it?
Oh, yeah!
Well, I want one, too.
I don't want it.
You don't want it.
I want it.
Okay, fine.
I'm glad.
The biggest fan of this radio program is my manager, Okkie.
Okki.
Can I have it next time I come?
She's a fan.
I'd like to give her the twist I just gave you.
I'd like to give it to her.
I'm flattered, but thank you.
Yay!
Vote.
Yes, sir.
End
Yes Exit
What did you get?
Oh
Start
just the party 2024
Yes, sir.
What's this?
That was a big story.
I can't tell you how much we've talked about it.
I'd like to thank all of you who came to see the event, and thank you to the staff for their hard work, and I'm sure that you've seen the distribution as well.
As those of you who went to the event will know, the event was held for two days, with a few live performers and a few live performers, but the content was all different.
The contents were all different from each other, from the unit to the shuffle to our own songs.
And the tick-top shows all the movements of the audience, and I was able to take pictures from close up.
It was a lot of fun, but it was difficult to move around.
It was very difficult to get off the stage and climb up to the top of the stage.
When the song starts, you have to get off the stage, turn around, and climb up. It was like, “Oh, we have to go up already, or we'll never make it in time.
Hey, TukTuk medley, it's time to take pictures, right?
What do you call it? There were some teams that were used to the TukTuk medley, and some that were not so used to it.
You were amazing, weren't you, Tokisen-chan?
You were amazing.
Well, you know...
Well, you know, there's an order, so everyone has to stand in a line, but...
But it really didn't go well.
Everyone was so polite, one by one, I guess.
He was sending many suits to the camera, so...
I was sitting there wondering if it's okay for us to sit on our backs...
Yes, but you know...
Lately, there are so many shirts...
Well, we were thinking that we would like to get the word out somehow.
Yes, that's right.
We're doing it, right?
We have to do it that slowly.
I realized that if I don't take it that slowly, I won't be able to get a good shot.
After that, everyone posted the pictures, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
I was so surprised when I saw my picture.
“Is this how everyone else does it?
Like this, you broke your shoulder, and then you just slipped out...
But I found a really cute video of Rika on X!
I found a video that was getting a lot of views.
I was watching it thinking how cute you are!
I'm so glad.
Did you see one like that?
You guys did a great job, you know, taking the pictures and making them look good now.
And then you processed them beautifully afterwards.
Thank you very much!
For taking lovely pictures of me.
I'm so glad.
Thank you very much.
Of course, the possibility of taking pictures is one of the things that made a lasting impression on me.
The medley of each day.
Yes, yes, yes!
Especially for me.
Why... by grade?
Yes, yes, yes.
Hapilable
I was allowed to play Hapirable
This was the Jun Nohara family
With kids of the same generation, of course, the three of us, always, Nonogawa, Mayuna, are of the same generation, but...
But it's different to work with another group of kids, isn't it? Yes. How did you interact with them?
Well, this time I got to talk to a lot of people.
Of course, if you're shy, of course, there was the STAPLA festival, but you didn't have much chance to talk to people on your own, especially if you were there for one day.
I was too busy to talk to many people. But we all talked about how we would like to learn dance and how we would do it, and it was very good.
The 07 generation really got together with everyone until the end of the day to make sure everything was okay.
They are so serious!
Yes, it was the first song that we came out from the back, from the middle, but even when we were waiting in the back, we were all singing together to make sure everything was okay.
We were doing it. I can say this now, but in the medley by grade, everyone was in their uniforms.
Did you notice that we were all wearing uniforms? Only Aaryn and I were wearing cardigans.
Oh, yeah! We're all friends with blazers and sailor suits and stuff, but we were the only ones in cardigans.
cardigans, did you hear that? I don't know, I don't know.
Well, I go to a private school, Ebisu Shugakko, and they let us wear uniforms, right?
So why are we wearing cardigans? I said, “Why are we wearing cardigans like this?
Because it's different from the current students.
They were saying that they dare to make the current students wear something colorful.
What a painful reality!
But yes, we were JKs in the Heisei era.
It's been a long time since I've worn a cardigan like that, so it was a lot of fun.
I was so happy, and we each wore them in different ways.
But I was waiting in the back, and I was at the same entrance as Arline.
I was on the other side of the stage, and I heard Arline's story a little bit...
Mayama has been wearing it for a long time, so it was very familiar to me.
I couldn't stand it, so I wrapped it around my waist.
She said it was so realistic
It was realistic, but that's the opposite of realistic
That's how our generation used to wear it.
For me, it's a familiar uniform.
I guess that's how I would have worn it if I had been in the same class.
I thought it was so cute.
I wanted to tie it around my waist too.
But Arline is the oldest on the staff.
I was born in December, so I was a little bit later than her.
So I thought I couldn't copy the way Arline wears hers.
I don't think I can emulate her style.
Me too.
I'm so excited...
I'm happy to say that I lived up to my expectations.
If you want, you know... everyone...
Are there any archives left?
Is it still there?
We're streaming it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'd love to. I'd love to.
Oh, yeah, you know, I just remembered...
Yes, I remember.
You know, we got all kinds of stuff for the staff, right?
Yes, yes, yes...
You know, I wrote my autograph on it.
Like a comment on the back.
I don't know.
You remember those?
You know, the kind of merchandise that came out?
Like an enthusiasm.
I see. You know what I mean? Oh, there was, like a keychain. Arline wrote on the back that Mayama was the oldest member of Stapa, and I was like, “You gotta be kidding me.
A gacha key chain. That's it. That's terrible. It's too much exploitation. It's too much manipulation of information.
Too much information manipulation, really. Adults are scary, so be careful, NONOKO.
That's all for now... Oh, last one! Let's go one more piece at a time.
Let's start. I also said, “I'm going to go out with a bang in the presence of other people, and the oldest person on the staff is Arline.
The one who said “Rasuliai. I had to do it again in 07. Let's do it.
I can't do it, guys.
I don't know about you guys.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Ended
Yes Thank you
Yes, thank you.
I want to tell Rika
This is
It says something.
I want to tell you something.
You like maratan, don't you?
I love
Maratan
I just got hooked on Maratan, too.
Yes, yes, yes.
But did you know that you can make it at home? Oh, really? I didn't know that.
I want to talk to you about this, but my nose is a little sore right now.
My nose hurts a little too much. What? What? They have all the ingredients for maratan at the supermarket.
Oh, I see. Then make it.
Oh!
Malathane is sold by weight, so if you put in as much as you like, it can get quite expensive.
It's true that there are many restaurants like that. There are many malatang restaurants where you can put in as many ingredients as you like, or sell them by weight.
I want to put in as much of what I like as I like.
So I looked up the recipe on Tik-Tok and made it, but I heard it's on there, so what do I need?
Well, you can go to a supermarket and buy a bottle of Mara, the kind of Mara that you find in drugstores and such.
You can buy a bottle of marler in the supermarket, and you can mix it with water and put it in and take it out and put it in and take it out and put it in and put it in.
I also add vegetables that I really like, and I also add thick vermicelli, which is sold at supermarkets these days, right?
I wanted to put a boiled egg, so I put it in.
I wanted to add a boiled egg, so I put it in.
I wanted you to make this for me. Thank you! Do you want to try it?
I have some of that “mara jang” stuff at home, but I don't know what to do with it, so I just fry it up.
I just make spicy stir-fries anyway.
I see.
Milk, water and broth?
Dashi? Dashi? Dashi?
Dashi, dashi, dashi, dashi.
Like beef broth? Yes, that's right.
I used it.
If you want to make it hotter, you can add soybean paste.
You can also adjust the spiciness.
I don't like spicy food, so you can add a little bit.
It's good.
It was really good.
Let's give it a try!
Rika probably won't make it.
She'll make it!
I will. As expected.
I will!
We've been waiting for you for a long time.
Thank you for telling me.
Do you cook much?
No, I'm really not very good at cooking.
You're not?
I'm training for when I start living on my own.
I'm training. Sometimes.
Oh.
When will you live on your own?
It's important, isn't it?
I've been making marathons lately.
I made maratan.
What else?
I helped my mom fry mackerel in vinegar.
With fish? Vinegared pork?
That's right, that's right.
Don't you think sweet-and-sour pork has a real homey flavor?
Yes, it does.
Yes.
You know...
I don't have any sweet-and-sour pork at home, but the Chinese restaurant where we used to go to eat with my family had black-and-white sweet-and-sour pork.
I was really shocked when I first saw ketchup flavored Sushi pork in my lunch box.
Indeed.
What kind of Sour Pork?
I was the ketchup one.
It's ketchup.
Is it in there? Fruit.
I didn't put fruit.
You didn't put fruit in it.
I was wondering why Chinese food is so different from sweet-and-sour pork.
I'm sorry, I just got curious.
I'm sorry, I was just curious, but I'm sorry.
We are like this... that's all... a Yukari-de-fu-fu survey.
I'm sorry, I was just wondering if it's different.
I don't think so...
Pineapple I can forgive
I can't!
I'll just rip it off and eat it.
Maybe worse, but I would scrape it off and eat it normally and deliciously, at the end of the day.
I want to eat it as a fruit.
As fruit, I know, I know.
It's not that I absolutely hate it.
I like it, you know.
I don't allow it. I can't allow it.
I was surprised. Because you suddenly came to me with a comment saying “I can't forgive you.
I thought I said something bad.
I can't forgive you.
There are people who can't tolerate all pineapple, right?
I like it a lot.
Like pineapple hamburgers.
I like those things too. I forgive.
I don't like them. And people who say they love it.
I understand.
I may not be able to forgive them.
Come on, then, continue. I'm going to do a project like this.
It's called “A Joyful and Happy November!
It's almost like I was talking about the month of November earlier,
In the script, there are various projects related to November written like a restaurant menu,
You can choose whatever you like.
I will choose what I want to do.
What will you choose?
What do you want to do? What do you want?
What do you want?
Well, first of all, let's post our favorite books and cartoons for the fall reading season!
I'd like to do it!
Great!
Speaking of manga, Rika, I know you watch a lot of manga and anime,
Do you have any? Recently, I really like it.
You know what?
I mean, it's been a favorite of mine for quite a while now.
It's called “Oshi ni Amagami Hair” (Sweet Hair for Oni).
I'd like to recommend it to Nonoka, who likes shoujo manga.
It's by Suzuki Julietta-sensei.
She writes “Kami hajimashita desu” and “Kamisama hajimashita”.
I think it's written by the same teacher who writes “Kami wo Shitajitate” and “Kami wo Shitajitate”.
The vampire girl is a nerdy girl.
And...
And she comes to the real world like this.
And then she finds a boy who looks like her
It's a romantic comedy.
It's a romantic comedy, but it's also pretty funny, and it's kind of easy to read, so...
I love vampire stories, so... but... if you're not into vampires... you're not going to like this.
I'm sure you'll find it very interesting and easy to read.
It's got some cute scenes, but it also has that funny element.
I've been reading Osuniyamagami for quite a while now.
I've been reading it for quite a while now, and there's a new book out, so please take a look if you like it.
Thank you very much.
Then, let's move on to my next one.
I'm going to make a comic book too.
I've been saying this for quite a while.
Yamada-kun and Level 99's Kora Slaughter manga is my favorite.
Volume 10 was released just a few days ago!
Congratulations!
It was released on Friday, the 22nd.
I was working on the Stardust Party staff at the time, so I couldn't go buy it, so my mom bought it for me and I read it yesterday.
I read it yesterday.
It was really great!
Yamada-kun is going to be made into a live-action movie in March!
Yes, Emina and I made a big fuss about it
Oh, you made a fuss?
I'm so excited about it that the three of us are talking about going to see it as a reward for SSA.
The 10th volume of the latest book has just been released, and I've already read the 10th volume once more yesterday, so I'm looking forward to it.
I'm so hooked again that I'm thinking of rereading the whole book from the beginning.
Yamada-kun...
high school sound boy college girl rap 6 rice that starts through a game of exterior Yes, that's right
It's already been 10 volumes, so it's been quite a while since Kyunker was released.
So there was a time when I forgot about it... but it's well known and there was a time when I forgot about it... but then I thought... when will it be released next?
I looked up when it was going to be released next, and I realized it was going to be released at 10:00 p.m. just before the release.
I'm so happy.
It's frustrating when it's too far away.
If it's too far away.
I'm always looking forward to it.
I was so happy to find it again just before it went on sale.
It's wonderful.
It's great.
You're right, if I don't listen to it, I forget about it.
So you're a comics guy.
Yes, I am.
I'm not a comic book guy, not an e-comic book guy.
I look at e-comics, but I want to hold it in my hand.
I want to hold it in my hand, so I can look back at it anytime.
That's why I recommend Yamada-kun and Resol and Kimura Kiji-kun's Consul.
Yes, by all means, volume 10 is easy to read.
I wonder how many volumes my favorite Tenjin is now? I think it's still around 10.
I think it's still around 10, so please check it out.
I think it's not even 10 yet.
So, one more question.
Let's go.
What would you like?
What?
What do you want?
Okay, let's see.
I've got some flippers and stuff for you.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Let's take a Kanji quiz related to autumn.
I'd like to try.
Oh!
Kanji quiz related to autumn?
Don't write the answers in the comments, guys.
Please do.
Mr. TP has already told us.
We've already got the kanji.
If it's a few meals, it's right... water... for now... leave it to me... please...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes...
I'm confident about this one.
I'm a junior high school girl... in the fall...
There are tests and stuff.
I can't do anything... but I've got it!
I've got it. I haven't seen it.
Okay, one at a time.
Let's start with “Nono”.
Yes...
You're not wrong, are you?
Yes, you're wrong, it's a fish, a fish!
My answer is... that way.
Yay!
I know!
This is...
I cook.
I don't really cook at all.
But I understand.
You know it when you see it.
I can read it.
Question 2.
Cosmos.
What's this? Cosmos?
What's cosmos?
Nanana...
Ki no ko...
Episode 2 Explanation
I don't understand
I really don't understand Kino
Ch Candy
I really don't get it.
Cosmos
What?
Cosmos?
Did you know there was such a thing as cosmos?
That flower.
Was there?
Cosmos.
Cosmos
Sei-no-Sei-no-Sei-no-Sei-no-Sei-no-U
Okay, then.
First, let's start with Mononoke-san
Cosmos
New
Something new...
Something new.
Is it the name of a dish? Cosmos.
Cosmos
Chinese cosmos.
Yes, sir.
It's hard to say after that.
I did this.
Cosmos
But...
What's the right answer?
What is it?
We're close.
That's right!
Autumn cherry blossoms.
Autumn cherry blossoms are cosmos.
Autumn. Autumn.
Autumn, autumn
Cosmos with autumn cherry blossoms
Yes!
I thought it was a tiny one.
Terrible.
We are terrible.
Yes, last one, Ginkgo.
What?
What? Ginkgo?
What? Do you know what that is? What?
Ginkgo?
But you think you know what it is, but it doesn't come to you?
I know, I know.
The plant ginkgo.
Ginkgo biloba? Not the stomach ginkgo.
Oh, you got away with that one.
Ginkgo.
What was it?
What?
Wait.
You've definitely seen it before, right?
What?
Huh?
It's called a ginko tree, isn't it? You sometimes feel together with “ginko no ki”, right?
Icho... what?
I don't know...
I don't understand. Icho...
What? You know?
Wait a minute, really, really, I'll make an excuse now.
I've been really bad at kanji since elementary school, and I've never scored 100 on a kanji test.
So..,
I thought I was done with it, that I was getting better at performing.
I didn't even do my homework.
I didn't do any homework. Only the Chinese character homework.
Like what's under the ginkgo tree?
What's that thing under the ginkgo?
That way.
What? Wait, wait, wait.
I don't understand.
What?
Huh?
What? Wait a minute.
This...
I'm also using some kind of eraser fluid when I do this.
Yes!
Then, Nonoko, please.
Yes, sir.
Fallen Leaves
What is it?
I'm here.
Shoes
I wanted to write “butterfly” but I didn't know how to spell it.
Ichoha.
Like Ichoha
Ichoha
What?
What's the answer?
Ah, gingko!
Ahhhhhhh!
You read “gingko” and think “ginkgo”.
I see.
Gingko for ginkgo.
I see, if you read gingko tree
Gingko tree
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wow.
Huh?
Yes, we
I've just shown you something a little embarrassing.
I know it's too late for me, but I'm still a student, so hang in there.
Can you hang in there?
I'm a sophomore in high school.
I can still do my best
Do your homework.
Yes, I will.
And that's it.
The 75th ending of the showroom is here in no time!
Okay, bye.
Shall we do it first?
First of all, let's do this!
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugakku Christmas Show 2024 Twinkle Twinkle!
Twinkle Twinkle, right?
Twinkle Twinkle Ebisu Star is coming on December 14th!
I'm here to use the twinkle twinkle from last time.
Yes, it's J. Comarajage!
This is Rika's performance!
Even if you can't feel it, you can direct it!
I'm sure you've been thinking about the set up a lot...
The 5 o'clock set was amazing, wasn't it?
Yes, there were some interesting 5 o'clock moments.
But, you know, a lot of people have already bought the tickets.
But for those who couldn't buy it, we'll do something about it.
Yes, we are now selecting the best ones to show to those who couldn't afford it.
We are now in the process of selecting the best ones so that those who couldn't afford them can see them somehow.
I'll be putting on a production.
Yes, and...
The 15th anniversary of Ebisu Chugaku University Eikai 2025 Band Brave will be held at Saitama Super Reno on March 20, 2025!
Did it end yesterday?
Yesterday, too, the registration was closed temporarily.
I think there will be another chance for you to buy the tickets from here.
Thank you very much for your cooperation!
I'll do my best.
We will do our best.
We'll be waiting for you.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm Shia Sha going public for Road to Sai Tama.
Thank you all so much for watching the show so far.
I'd like to show you a little something as a token of my appreciation.
Here she is.
That's a hint.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I dragged you all this way.
I couldn't show you everything.
It's just a hint.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry... I'm sorry... I'm sorry... I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
There's a magnificent Ebisu-sama here, isn't there?
Yes, the upper part is here, and the lower part is like this.
I don't show his face.
No face.
Yes, his feet...
Your legs are so beautiful.
They are beautiful.
Who is it?
Oh, yeah, you're in.
You'll get a kick out of the station, really. Yes, you will.
They're nice feet.
Yes, by all means, the face will be shown later.
But since you've all seen it so far, I'd like to show you a few shots that were lost.
I'd like to show you a shot that was lost, just for you.
Here's the shot that didn't make it.
What is it? It's dark? Uh, what's wrong?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
I did my best. I shot it on film.
Film looks like this, doesn't it?
Yes, with film, the flash didn't catch up with the picture.
What you just saw was a picture taken with a smartphone, which everyone is using these days.
I took a picture taken with a smartphone, which everyone is using these days, and processed it in a film style to make it look fashionable and current.
I'm not sure if you can see it clearly or if you can't see it at all, but you can't see it at all.
I'm sure you can tell that only Riko knows that, but the rest of them are all white.
I'm sure you'll get a good laugh out of this, but if this were to be published as an “asher,” I'm sure you wouldn't get it.
I'd like to learn how to wear white in such a situation, right?
Yes, well, there are a lot of people during the daytime, but... you know...
It's nighttime, but we've chosen a time when junior high school students are allowed to go out.
And here's a shot of them off duty.
Yes, they seem to be having fun.
You can see that there are a few people here and there.
And here's the candy girl from Ebichu!
And here's the candy girl in the shrimp.
I'm sorry...
Asha, if I show it to the public, you'll see...
She's smiling in the candy.
She's smiling.
Yes, I'm smiling.
It's been such a fun day, hasn't it?
These candy girls...
Yes, they did their best.
I got it in one shot.
Now, now, now!
You know, when you've been an idol for a long time...
It's been four years.
I've been doing it for four years now... you're not afraid of people in town, are you?
I can say, “No problem” My heart is getting stronger and stronger
So, please look forward to the release of the next issue of the magazine.
Let's announce the final ranking.
Thank you Natsumi, thank you Simon, thank you Nana, and thank you 1 oms.
Thank you very much!
e...
The last time I went to the showroom, the excitement was almost 6,500.
We'll let you know the next episode as soon as it's decided, so be sure to follow the official Ebichu x page!
I'm so glad you're following us!
Thank you very much!
Please listen to Stand fm Artie Pee's hard work on the radio!
And that's it, that's it for week 1 of the series.
Bye-bye!
Thank you very much for listening.